So it was brought to my attention that Joelle Santana was saying that reading is not important.
That literacy is not important, but financial literacy is.
I'm not going to even argue the point because it's not a valid point.
I would, however, love to get in touch with Joelle's what's really good and have an offline
combo. As an educator, as an artistic intellectual, as a radical black woman, I just feel like it's so
important that we each one teach one. And I'm more than happy to share my knowledge and time and energy
with the brother on this topic. I think it would be really valuable and helpful. And speaking of
valuable and helpful, when I first moved to Harlem in 2003, Joelle's brother twin made sure that the
cats on the block did not mess with me. It looked out for me. And that's something that I will always
cherish because when you're moving into a new hood, you want to make sure that you are protected. And
they looked out. And while we're addressing Dipset, Joelle's dip, dip, Santana, set, set. So anybody out
there, if you are still connected to Joelle's, let them know that I'm looking for them and I'd love to
talk. And I'm here in New York. At one point in time, Jim Jones called me a dummy on the internets
for supporting Biden. And he was right. It's a summer with Miami.